wanderfly.com 2011-12-05

# Privacy | Travel News, Travel Advice, Vacation Recommendations | Wanderfly Blog

WHAT INFORMATION DO WE COLLECT?  
We collect information from you when you register on our site, place an order, subscribe to our newsletter, respond to a survey, fill out a form, submit information or request information.

When placing an order or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter information such as your name, email address, mailing address, phone number or credit card information. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

WHAT DO WE USE YOUR INFORMATION FOR?  
Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

To process transactions: your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.  
To personalize your experience: your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs.  
To improve our site: we continually strive to improve our site offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you.  
To improve customer service: your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs.  
To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature.  
To send periodic emails: the email address you provide for order processing, may be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order, in addition to receiving occasional company news, updates, related product or service information, etc.

If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.

HOW DO WE PROTECT YOUR INFORMATION?  
We implement a variety of physical, electronic, and administrative security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order or access your personal information.

We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Payment gateway providers database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential.

After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, mailing address, phone number, etc.) will be kept on file for more than 60 days in order to expedite and improve future visits and transactions that may occur on our site.

DO WE USE COOKIES?  
Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer’s hard drive through your web browser (if you allow) that enables the site’s or service provider’s systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information.

We use cookies to help us remember and process your purchased items, understand and save your preferences for future visits and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future.

DO WE DISCLOSE ANY INFORMATION TO OUTSIDE PARTIES?  
We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our site, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or other’s rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

THIRD PARTY LINKS  
We may include or offer third party products or services on our site. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

CALIFORNIA ONLINE PRIVACY PROTECTION ACT COMPLIANCE  
Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to comply with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.

As part of the California Online Privacy Protection Act, all users of our site may make any changes to their information at anytime by logging into their account settings and editing their information.

CHILDREN’S ONLINE PRIVACY PROTECTION ACT COMPLIANCE  
We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act). Our site, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older. We do not intend to collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age.

TERMS OF SERVICE  
Please also visit our Terms of Service section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our site at <http://blog.wanderfly.com/terms>

YOUR CONSENT  
By using our site, you consent to our Privacy Policy.

CHANGES TO OUR PRIVACY POLICY  
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page, send an email notifying you of any changes, and/or update the Privacy Policy modification date below.

This policy was last modified on June 24, 2010

CONTACTING US  
If there are any questions regarding this Privacy Policy you may contact us at the information below.

Wanderfly Inc.  
447 Broadway, 2nd Floor  
New York, NY 10013  
USA
